[
    {
        "question": "An unconditional order by a creditor to a debtor requiring payment on a specified date is called",
        "optionA": "promissory note",
        "optionB": "letter of credit",
        "optionC": "money order",
        "optionD": "Niger",
        "answer": "bill of exchange"
    },

    {
        "question": "The effective dissemination of information about products is a social responsibility of a company to its",
        "optionA": "shareholders",
        "optionB": "management",
        "optionC": "employees",
        "optionD": "consumers",
        "answer": "consumers"
    },

    {
        "question": "The trade that takes place when imported goods are re-exported is known as",
        "optionA": " entrepot trade",
        "optionB": "import trade",
        "optionC": "export trade",
        "optionD": "visible trade",
        "answer": "entrepot trade"
    },

    {
        "question": "Commerce aids the development of any economy as it",
        "optionA": " provides for proper accountability ",
        "optionB": "encourages the reduction of inflation",
        "optionC": "enhances the even distribution of wealths the living standard",
        "optionD": "improves the living standard",
        "answer": "improves the living standard"
    },

    {
        "question": "Awarding scholarships and sponsoring sports by a business organization are example of?",
        "optionA": "advertising strategy",
        "optionB": "economic responsibility",
        "optionC": "marketing strategy",
        "optionD": "social responsibility",
        "answer": "social responsibility"
    },

    {
        "question": "An authorâ€™s exclusive right to his published and unpublished works is known as?",
        "optionA": "authors right",
        "optionB": "constitution right",
        "optionC": "patent right",
        "optionD": "copyright",
        "answer": "copyright"
    },

    {
        "question": "Under the endowment policy, the money handed over to the insured at the expiration of the stipulated time or at death is the?",
        "optionA": "indemnity",
        "optionB": "surrender value",
        "optionC": "insurance premium",
        "optionD": "lump sum benefit",
        "answer": "lump sum benefit"
    },

    {
        "question": "The machine used for sending telex messages is known as a ",
        "optionA": " radar",
        "optionB": "teleprinter",
        "optionC": "fax machine",
        "optionD": "dictaphone",
        "answer": "fax machine"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these insurance principles requires a close connection between the actual loss suffered and the risk insured?",
        "optionA": "indemnity",
        "optionB": "Contribution",
        "optionC": "proximate cause",
        "optionD": "Subrogation",
        "answer": "proximate cause"
    },

    {
        "question": "The organizational structure that relates the positions of specialist to the line mangers is called?",
        "optionA": "line structure",
        "optionB": "functional structure",
        "optionC": "line and staff structure",
        "optionD": "staff structure",
        "answer": "staff structure"
    },

    {
        "question": "The unit through which result of a processed data are displayed is the",
        "optionA": "logic unit",
        "optionB": " display unit",
        "optionC": "control unit",
        "optionD": "output unit",
        "answer": "output unit"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to inform the addressee that a registered parcel is ready for collection?",
        "optionA": " Express label",
        "optionB": "Counterfoil",
        "optionC": "Telegram",
        "optionD": "Slip",
        "answer": "Slip"
    },

    {
        "question": "The type of computer commonly found in office is?",
        "optionA": "laptop",
        "optionB": "desktop",
        "optionC": "the mainframe computer",
        "optionD": "the hybrid computer",
        "answer": "the hybrid computer"
    },

    {
        "question": "The temporary insurance certificate issued to the insured before drawing up a policy is a?",
        "optionA": "cover note",
        "optionB": "proposal form",
        "optionC": "time policy",
        "optionD": "testimonial",
        "answer": "cover note"
    },

    {
        "question": "The mode of transporting crude oil to the ports for export purposes is by",
        "optionA": "tanker",
        "optionB": "rail",
        "optionC": "pipeline",
        "optionD": "road",
        "answer": "pipeline"
    }
]